# Kyle Owen Ga

gakyleowen@gmail.com (+63) 939-119-2839 DECA HOMES Cabantian Davao City, Davao Region

### **Summary**

An ambitious software engineer with three years of experience in Javascript, PHP, React.js, Vue.js, Express.js, Laravel, MongoDB, Postgresql, MVC, Graphql API, and REST API. Constant learner and ability to adapt to new technologies. Possess strong communication and team management skills.

#### **Education**

# Information Technology

AMA Computer College • Davao City, Davao Region 2019-2022 Dean's Lister

08/2022

#### **Skills**

JavaScript, PHP, React.js, Next.js, Express.js, Vue.js, Laravel, Wordpress

MongoDB, Postgre, Mysql, Git, GitHub

### Experience

## Developer II

FWD Springboard Student Challenge • Davao City, Davao Region

09/2021 - 11/2021

- Won Top 3 in the National Level
- Developed a social media mobile application (with React Native) that allows easy access to insurance globally

# Developer II

Web-based Fire Safety Inspection Certification System of Bureau of Fire Protection (Davao City) • Davao City, Davao Region

02/2022 - 05/2022

· Built the front-end for the Certification System for Applicants and Bureau of Fire Protection Employees

## **Developer Lead**

Fire Safety Virtual Inspection • Davao City, Davao Region

02/2022 - 04/2022

• Created a Video Conferencing Web application for Fire Safety Inspection as an optional feature.

#### **Projects**

Fire Safety Virtual Inspection - (Video Conferencing App for Fire Safety Inspection)

BlackedMarket - (Ecommerce web app)

Get To Know Me - (Portfolio website)